socialadr.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy | SocialAdr - Social Media Marketing Services

We know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the SocialAdr website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this privacy policy. 

This privacy policy covers SocialAdr's treatment of personal information that SocialAdr gathers when you are on the SocialAdr website. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that SocialAdr does not own or control, or to individuals that SocialAdr does not employ or manage. 

### Information Collected by SocialAdr

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website, which is to enable users to discover and share information with one another. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our SocialAdr users: 

**1\. Information You Provide to Us:**

We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. 

\- Registration: In order for you to use SocialAdr services, such as submitting new links to the website, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require your personal information (including your name and e-mail address). 

\- User Profile: To allow you to express yourself beyond the information collected during registration, we enable you to provide additional information, such as a bio, favorite URLs, and instant messaging IDs. In addition, you may choose to include photos of yourself in your profile. As indicated below, in the section titled "Sharing Your Information", you can control how your information is displayed and used. 

**2\. Automatic Information:**

\- We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. SocialAdr and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, SocialAdr cookie information, and the page you requested. SocialAdr uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website. 

\- SocialAdr may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed. This includes User Profile pages. 

\- Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While SocialAdr will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available. 

### E-mail Communications

SocialAdr is concerned about your privacy and will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the "Sharing Your Information" section below. SocialAdr may send out e-mails with SocialAdr-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions. You may also receive notification e-mails from SocialAdr, informing you of actions (e.g. friend requests) that have been performed on the site. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please visit the Email Preferences section of your User Profile and/or follow the instructions contained in the unwanted e-mail message. However, please note that in all cases you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us. 

### Cookies

\- Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we tranfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. SocialAdr cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is. 

\- The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of SocialAdr's coolest features. 

\- Some of our business partners, like our advertisers, may use cookies on our website. We have no access to, or control over, these cookies. 

### Sharing Your Information

Because SocialAdr enables people to discover and share information with one another, information about the people who use SocialAdr is an integral part of the SocialAdr experience. Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below. 

\- SocialAdr Personnel: SocialAdr personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of SocialAdr business. 

\- Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if SocialAdr, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred. 

\- Protection of SocialAdr and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of SocialAdr, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

\- User Profile information: Information collected during registration and subsequent visits, such as your full name and location, may be displayed to other SocialAdr users in your User Profile. The User Profile is the area on SocialAdr where we allow you to tell other SocialAdr users about yourself and your interests. You may control what personal information is displayed in your User Profile by visiting the Privacy Settings section of your User Profile. 

\- Member Directory: The e-mail address that you submit upon registration will be searchable by other SocialAdr users who know you by your email address, unless you choose to opt out of this feature. This is primarily so that other users can find you to establish friendship through SocialAdr. You may opt-out of this feature by visiting the Privacy Settings section of your User Profile. 

\- Social sharing of data: SocialAdr allows other users to browse stories that you have Socialized, submitted, blogged, or commented on. This information is made available via your User Profile or within the permalink URL of the story on which you performed the action. SocialAdr may choose to post this data on other site features. 

\- Friends' Activity: Much like other online social networks, SocialAdr allows non-friends to browse your friends' activity. 

\- With Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information. 

### Keeping Information Secure

\- Your SocialAdr account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. Protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer. 

\- Only employees who need personal information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices. 

### Ways to Control Display and Use of Your Information

\- As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, but then you may be unable to use certain features on our website, such as posting new links. 

\- By visiting your User Profile, you can correct, amend, add or delete personal information on our website. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. 

\- You may request deletion of your SocialAdr account by contacting us via the Contact form. 

\- If you do not wish to receive e-mail from us or other SocialAdr users, please visit the Email Preferences section of your User Profile and/or follow the instructions contained in the unwanted e-mail message. 

\- However, please note that you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us. 

\- If you do not wish to have people who know you by your email address find you via the Member Directory service, please visit the Privacy Settings section of your User Profile to opt out of this feature. 

\- As explained earlier, the "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. Please note, however, that if your browser does not accept cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of some of our attractive features. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

SocialAdr may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the SocialAdr website so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed. 

### Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit SocialAdr website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, and arbitration of disputes. 

### Effective Date of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of July 1, 2009
